tradingsetupsreview.com 2014-12-04

# Privacy Policy - Trading Setups Review

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at galenwoods@tradingsetupsreview.com.

At www.tradingsetupsreview.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.tradingsetupsreview.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.tradingsetupsreview.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

www.tradingsetupsreview.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.tradingsetupsreview.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.tradingsetupsreview.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you may also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)
  *  The cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/support/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on your site. You may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you may also opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.tradingsetupsreview.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.tradingsetupsreview.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.tradingsetupsreview.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We have implemented Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting based on Google Display Advertising. Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. We use the data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics to understand the profile of our typical reader in order to increase the relevancy of our website content.
